Come with me as I satisfy my pregnant
wife's cravings with a four-course meal
on a budget of $5 per person. She's just
about halfway through her pregnancy and
[music] thankfully things have settled
down after a pretty rough first
trimester. However, her taste buds are
still all over the place. Every meal
[music] needs bold flavors and plenty of
variety. So, one of my jobs these days
is being the food delivery rider.
Obviously, that's a much easier job than
what she is going through, so I'm not
complaining. Plus, it gives me a good
excuse to squeeze in a few bike rides,
which [music] I otherwise haven't had
much time for. So, what's on our $5 menu
today? Now, Singapore has a reputation
for being expensive, but one thing that
can be surprisingly affordable is
freshly cooked [music] meals. And this
is thanks to our hawker culture. For our
international viewers, hawker centers
are basically open-air food courts with
rows of independent stalls, [music] each
specializing in a particular set of
dishes. Bold flavors and variety are not
a problem here. Not only is this where
you'll find the most affordable meals in
the country, many locals will tell you
it's where you'll find the best-tasting
food, period. Our meal for two cost just
over $10, which works out to about $5
per person. But the wife is satisfied
and the baby probably is, too. And
[music] that's priceless.